The perfect staycation
The Resort is a horror film directed by Taylor Chien.
Four friends head to Hawaii to investigate reports of a haunting at an
abandoned resort in hopes of finding the infamous Half-Faced Girl.
When they arrive, they soon learn you should be careful what you wish for.
Lex, played by Bianca Haase.
Chris, played by Brock O'Hurn.
Sam, played by Michael Vlamis.
Bree, played by Michelle Randolph.
Detective, played by Dave Sheridan.
Mike, played by Dante Jimenez.
The Resort is a 2021 American horror film written and directed by Taylor Chien.
It stars Bianca Haase, Brock O'Hurn, Michael Vlamis, and Michelle Randolph.
The movie was shot in 2019, and hip-hop artist Quavo helped produce it
after being encouraged by main producer Will Meldman.
The film focuses on four friends who head to Hawaii to investigate reports of a haunting
at an abandoned resort in hopes of finding the infamous "Half-Faced Girl."
The film explores themes of helicopter, hawaii, haunting, waterfall, resort.
The tone is dark.